I'm about to cause an earthquake in the design world.
All thanks to Skill's insane reverse engineering feature for prompts.
Making it super easy for even complete beginners to create designs.
Before we start designing, we usually look for some reference cases.
This one looks pretty good.
Don't blink.
Now, watch me work my magic.
First, we're going to feed this reverse-engineered prompt into Skill.
And now, let's generate it.
And just like that, we've got our detailed prompt.
Here, the main visual element is the core of the entire image.
And now, let's change the design elements to fruits.
Let's go ahead and generate the skill.
This will then call upon the NANA AI model.
And just like that, the main visual of the poster has been changed to a fruit element.
And you can also have it generate four different versions for you.
giving you more options to choose from.
Of course, you can also specify your own custom settings.
Let's go ahead and select the landmark buildings from these cities.
Then, we'll change the main visual elements to these four landmark buildings.
Alright, let's go ahead and generate it.
See that?
Skill will interpret this as having those landmark buildings displayed inside a picture frame.
But what I really want is for *all* the visual elements to be replaced with landmark buildings.
At this point, all you have to do is tell Skill,
to change all the elements into landmark buildings.
Alright, let's hit generate again.
See that?
This is exactly the effect I was going for.
Then, you can go ahead and edit the text.
and you can easily change the text.
This method really makes the whole process super simple.
You can repeat this process for any other settings you want to tweak.
So, since you've made it this far,
So, go ahead and explore it for yourselves!